Contact

Adama, Ethiopia +251996529960 (Mobile) duresawata21@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/duresawata-6397a51a9 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Full-Stack Development
Web Development
Back-End Web Development

Duresa wata

Upwork Freelancer

Nazret

Summary

Hello, my name is Duresa. I am Full-stack Developer with 4+ years of experiance. I am well-versed in back-end frameworks such as Django and Flask. Also I have rich experience in front-end frameworks such as Boostrap. Currently I'm freelancer on upwork. for more information contact me on duresawata21@gmail.com or you can find my works on my github account. Thank you, I look forward to working with you.

Experience

ICPC - International Collegiate Programming Contest Competitive Programming September 2020 - Present (1 year 8 months) Nazret, Ethiopia

Upwork

Full-stack Developer September 2020 - Present (1 year 8 months) Nazret, Ethiopia

Adama Science and Technology University Student

October 2019 - Present (2 years 7 months)

Nazret, Ethiopia

Education

Adama science and technology university Bsc, computer science and engineering